Guide to the Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency (HER) Records 2000-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Committee Records, 1979-2011
  - Community Outreach Committee, 2003-2011
    - Nomination Form – Stream Award for Excellence in Women Health, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Publications Report – Health Notes, 2003; 2007; 2009 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - 14th Annual Women and Girls' Good Health Scholarship Contest, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Essay Contest, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Winning Essay, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Outreach Committee Conference Call – Minutes, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Community Outreach Committee Meeting, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Nominees – Kathryn S. Stream Award for Excellence in Women's Health, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Essay Contest Winners, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Essays for Allison, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - 2007 Publication Distribution, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - The Publication Order Forms, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Scholarship Essay Grading Sheet, undated (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Scholarship Essay Contest, 2003; 2009-2011 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Scholarship Recipient, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Scholarship Recipient, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Development Committee, 1991-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13-17b)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1987-1988; 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Membership Committee, 1980-1997 (Box 2, Folder 20-24)
  - Corporate Sponsors and Memberships, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Lifetime Memberships, 1989-1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Medical Memberships, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Membership Address Labels, 1985-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Membership Contributions, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Membership Deleted/Non-Renewal List, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Membership Directory, 1989-1990, 1992-1998; 1992-1998 (Box 3, Folder 7-12)
  - Membership History, 1979-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Membership Rosters, 1980; 1983; 1986; 1989-1991; 1993; 1999 (Box 3, Folder 14-20a)
  - Membership Solicitations, 1991-1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Newsletters, 1980-1999 (Box 3, Folder 22-32, Box 4, Folder 1-9)
  - Newsletter Committee Correspondence, 1986-1999 (Box 4, Folder 10-13a)
  - Newsletter 5 1/4" Floppy Disks, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Nominating Committee, 1991-1993; 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 15-18)
  - Program Committee - Correspondence, 1981-2000 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Program Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 20-24)
  - Program Committee - Event Management, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Program Committee - Program Feedback Analysis, 1985-1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Program Committee - Programs, 1979-1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Program Committee - Potential Speakers/Topics, 1987-1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Program Committee - Potential Sites, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Program Committee - Meetings and Minutes, 1987-1995 (Box 5, Folder 4-4a)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1990-1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Public Relations Committee - Media Relations, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations Committee - News Clippings, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Public Relations Committee - Proofs, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Public Relations Committee - Tale of Tiger, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Volunteer Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1979-1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Committee Manual, 1997-1999 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Special Events, 1979-2008
  The Special Events series includes records of all events produced by the Women's Fund. This series has been divided into eight subseries based on the different groups of events: Annual Benefit Luncheons, John P. McGovern Fall Seminars, Spring Seminars, Lectures and Seminars, Membership Coffees, Professional Women's Luncheons, Outreach Events, Fundraising Events, and Speakers' Bureau. Photographs from Women's Fund special events can be found in the Photographs series.
  - Annual Benefit Luncheons, 1979-1989
    To raise the funds needed to support the goals of the Women's Fund, organizers established an Annual Benefit Luncheon in 1983, with humorist Erma Bombeck as the first featured speaker. Bombeck's charisma and the labors of Women's Fund volunteers drew 1,046 attendees and netted the organization nearly $25,000. Every year since, the Annual Benefit Luncheons and celebrities such as David Eisenhower, John Bradshaw, Ann Richards, and Liz Carpenter help raise money for the Women's Fund's education and outreach programs. Demonstrating remarkable fundraising skill, the Women's Fund invited Florence Henderson as the featured speaker in 2001, resulting in $150,000 net profit. Annual benefit materials were in good chronological order when received by the archives, but considerations for easy access and the volume of documents required imposing parallel subdivisions for each benefit year to create consistency among the events. The amount of material in some categories required splitting the materials chronologically into more than one folder.
    - Annual Benefit History
      - History, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - BBQ (Initiation Fundraiser), 1979
      - Attendance, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Expenses/Income, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Publicity, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 1st Annual Benefit Luncheon - Erma Bombeck, 1983
      - Attendance, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Expenses/Income, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Publicity, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 2nd Annual Benefit Luncheon - Cherry Boone O'Neill, 1984
      - Attendance, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Expenses/Income, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Publicity, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - 3rd Annual Benefit Luncheon - Norman Cousins, 1985
      - Attendance, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Expenses/Income, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Publicity, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - 4th Annual Benefit Luncheon - David Eisenhower, 1986
      - Attendance, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Expenses/Income, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Publicity, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - 5th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Liz Carpenter, 1987
      - Attendance, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Expenses/Income, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Publicity, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - 6th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Suzanne Somers, 1988
      - Attendance, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Expenses/Income, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Publicity, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 7th Annual Benefit Luncheon - John Bradshaw, 1989
      - Attendance, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Expenses/Income, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Publicity, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 8th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Robert Fulghum, 1990
      - Attendance, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Expenses/Income, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Publicity, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 9th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Ann Richards, 1991
      - Attendance, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Expenses/Income, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Publicity, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - 10th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Mary Higgins Clark, 1992
      - Attendance, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Expenses/Income, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Publicity, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - 11th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Moya Olsen Lear, 1993
      - Attendance, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Expenses/Income, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Publicity, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - 12th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Richard Lederer, 1994
      - Attendance, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Expenses/Income, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Publicity, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 13th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Janice Woods Windle, 1995
      - Attendance, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Expenses/Income, January-August 1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Expenses/Income, September-December 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Publicity, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 14th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Carol Saline, 1996
      - Attendance, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Expenses/Income, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Publicity, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 15th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Jayne Meadows, 1997
      - Attendance, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Expenses/Income, February-August 1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Expenses/Income, September-October 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Expenses/Income, November-December 1997 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Publicity, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Volunteer Organization, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - 16th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Rita Moreno, 1998
      - Attendance, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, November 1997-May 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, June-October 1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Corporate Sponsors, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Expenses/Income, April-September 1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Expenses/Income, October-December 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Publicity, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 17th Annual Benefit Luncheon - Emily Crosswell, 1999
      - Attendance, January-May 1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Attendance, June-October 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Celebrity/Event Arrangements, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Corporate Sponsors, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Expenses/Income, April-May 1999 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Expenses/Income, June-July 1999 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Expenses/Income, August 1999 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Expenses/Income, September 1999 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Expenses/Income, October 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Expenses/Income, November 1999-January 2000 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Sponsor Ticket Purchases, April-August 1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Sponsor Ticket Purchases, September-December 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - John P. McGovern Fall Seminars, 1991-1999
    John P. McGovern, M.D. is president of the boards of the John P. McGovern Foundation and the McGovern Fund for Behavioral Sciences. He is founder of the McGovern Allergy Clinic, the world's largest private allergy clinic. In 1991, Dr. McGovern endowed the Annual John P. McGovern Seminar for the Women's Fund. Each Fall Seminar covers a topic of interest to the Women's Fund membership. In this collection seven annual events dating from 1991 through 1999 are housed in seven folders.
    - 1st Annual - Carl Anderson - Addiction: Feeding a Hungry Heart, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 2nd Annual - Stuart Yudofsky - Challenge Inner Space, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 3rd Annual - Frank Smith - Interaction and Overmedication, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 4th Annual - Shearer - Allergies: The Immune System, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 5th Annual - Kathy Cronkite - Depression, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 8th Annual - William H. Boylstein, MD, Alice M. Gates, EdD - Everyday Depression: Recognizing and Taking Care of The Blues and The Blahs, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 5a)
    - 9th Annual - Linda Boerger Andrews, MD - Can Your Mind Ease Your Pain?, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 5b)
    - 18th Annual - Breast Cancer, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - 19th Annual - "Sleep of a Lifetime", 2010 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - 14th and 20th Annual, 2005; 2011 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Spring Seminars, 1981-1999
    Spring seminars began two years after the initiation of the Women's Fund, and became the spring counterpart of the Fall Benefit Luncheon. In 1992 friends of Wendy Haskell Meyer offered an endowment to support the annual spring seminar in her honor. Wendy Haskell Meyer had been an active member of the Women's Fund and wrote the first English edition of the The Primer on Women's Health. She died in 1987, and her obituaries are included in this subseries.
    - 3rd Annual - Combined Program, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Ronald L. Young - "Questions Women Most Often Ask Their Gynecologist," Jaime Cochran and Jean Burkham - "Rape Awareness: Prevention and Psychological Effects," Thomas Biggs - "Who Should Have Plastic Surgery"
    - 4th Annual - Joseph Goldzieher, Jaimie Cochran, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 5th Annual - Combined Program, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Joseph Goldzieher - "Update on Osteoperosis," John Stehlin, Jr. - "Cancer Prevention Do's, Don'ts, and Myths"
    - 6th Annual, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Lawrence Wharton - "Chemical Abuse in Women" Workshops - Jane Taylor - "What Every Woman Should Know About Breast Cancer," and Lisa Balick - "Burn-out: Are You a Candidate?"
    - 7th Annual, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Jeane Hester - "Advances in Cancer and Leukapheresis," Margaret Kripke - "Ultra-violet Induced Skin Cancer Including the Role of Immunology in Cancer and Aging," Louise Strong - "Family Heredity and Genetic Risk Factors in Cancer Occurrence"
    - 8th Annual, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Tom Blocher - "Five Steps to a Stronger Self," Dena Kindred - "The Fitness Fix"
    - 9th Annual - Rebecca Elon - Successful Aging - Attendance, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      "Health Aging: Myths and Facts," R. Rodney Howell - "The Child is Father to the Man: Aging and Genetics," Noranna Warner - "Aches and Pains, Creaks and Cracks: The Musculoskeletal System as It Gets Older," James Grotta - "Our Brain Drain: How Our Perceptions Change as We Age"
    - 9th Annual - Rebecca Elon - Successful Aging - Arrangements, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - 9th Annual - Rebecca Elon - Successful Aging - Income/Expense, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - 10th Annual - Superwoman Panel, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Margaret Maxey - "Women in a Technological Society: Confronting Faust and Frankenstein," Wayne Holtzman - "Body Image and Self Esteem"
    - 11th Annual - Parenting a Parent - Attendance, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - 11th Annual - Parenting a Parent - Arrangements, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - 11th Annual - Parenting a Parent - Income/Expenses, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - 11th Annual - Parenting a Parent - Publicity, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - 12th Annual - Jane Porcino - The Sensuous Older Woman, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - 13th Annual - Kathryn Cramer - Staying on Top in the Upside Down World of the 90's, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - 14th Annual - Wendy Haskell Meyer - Decision for Healthy Living in the 90s, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      Panel - Carolyn Moore - "Nutritional Controversies," John Foreyt - "Living without Dieting," Peter Jones - "Women & Heart Disease," Molly Gee - "Positive Eating"
    - 15th Annual - Wendy Haskell Meyer - Prime Time Women, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      B. J. Frye, Elsa Rosborough, and Eleanor Tinsley
    - 16th Annual - Wendy Haskell Meyer - Alternative Health Care, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      Kris Rogers - "Acupuncture," Jerry Martin - "Chiropractic," Gilbert Manso - "Vitamin Therapy"
    - 17th Annual - Wendy Haskell Meyer - Elizabeth Vliet - "Women's Health: Those Marvelous and Maddening Hormones", 1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Wendy Haskell Meyer - Obituaries, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Wendy Haskell Meyer - Spring Seminar "The Biology of Attachment," Speakers - Dr. Pat Love, Dr. Ruth Burgos-Sasscer, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 26a)
    - Wendy Haskell Meyers - Spring Seminar "Life Preservers," Harriet Lerner, PhD, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 26b)
  - Lectures/Seminars, 1987-1995
    Toward fulfilling its mission, the Women's Fund offered lectures and seminars on women's health problems, new technologies, and advances in disease treatment and management. Offered to the public as well as Women's Fund members, many of these lectures and seminars were free. Seminars are organized chronologically from 1987 through 1995.
    - Teenage Sexuality in the 80's: What Every Parent Should Know, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      Panel: Peggy Smith - "Teenage Sexuality," Sebastian Faro - "Sexually Transmitted Diseases," Susan Pokorny - "Teenage Pregnancy"
    - The Evolution of Women's Self Care, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      Panel: Bruce Shephard, Sebastian Faro, and Marian Wulf
    - How You Can Plan for Unexpected Financial and Emotional Responsibilities, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      Panel: R.H. Stevens and Guy Bond
    - Estrogen: Miracle or Myth? Baylor College of Medicine, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Parenting an Aging Parent, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      Panel: Linda Kaeser - "Aging Well," Dudley Pate - "Health Insurance," Robert Luchi - "Medical Issues," Nancy Wilson - "Community Resources," Anita Woods - "Social/Mental Well-Being"
    - Endometriosis, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      Panel: Ronald Young, Vicki Schnell, and Dorothy Roach
    - Dixie Melillo - Beauty and the Beast: Fighting on the Front Lines of the Battle Against Breast Cancer, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Woman to Woman: As Our Lives Unfold, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      Panel: Jaimie Cochran, Keith Smith, Catherine Maxwell Hees, and Susan Cohen
    - Woman to Woman: Breaking the Silence, Seminar on Violence in the Home, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      Panel: Judith McFarline, Carol Gee, Jeffry Basen-Engquist
    - Women and Heart Disease, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      Panel: Karlene Kerfoot, Gary Binder, and Susan Wilansky
    - The Latest and Greatest in New Technology, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      Panel: Susan Pinero, John Walsh, Caroline Fife, Richard Ruiz
    - Financial Management, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      Panel: Jeanne Lynch, Mary Bird Bowman
    - Fundraising Seminar Correspondence, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Hot Zones in Infectious Diseases Today, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - John Carr Donation Memorial Service Email Correspondence, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Program Lecture Series, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - The Junior League of Houston, Inc. 10th Anniversary Annual Fund, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - The Celebration of Excellence, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Management Assistance Program Certificates, 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - "What About Me?" Focus Group Participants, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - De Madres a Madres Program, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Hotline Numbers and Brochures, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Hotline Numbers - Resources, 1998; 2001; 2003 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Rice Practicum - Cathy Moore, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - What About Me? - Wheeler Avenue Focus Group, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - ExxonMobil Summer Program Intern, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - What About Me? Adult Focus Group, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - What About Me? Galveston, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - What About Me? Update - Articles, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - What About Me? Update - Focus Groups, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Evaluation on Health Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - What About Me? Update, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - What About Me? Evaluations, 2000-2003 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - What About Me? Evaluations for Repeat Customers, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - What About Me? Evaluations for Girls, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Health Education Programs, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Honoring Luncheon Committee Reply Forms, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Wendy Haskell Meyer Seminar, Benefit Luncheon, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - 4th Annual Women and Girls Good Health Day, Planning and Expenses, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Seminar Programs, Expenses, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - What About Me? Curriculum, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - What About Me? Update, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - What About Me? Blank Evaluations, undated (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - What About Me? Campaign Logos, undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Identity Campaign Materials, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - What About Me? Misc. Materials, undated (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Wendy Haskell Meyer Seminar, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Smart Lunch on the Run, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - "Creating Emotional Balance in Every Day Life" PowerPoint Presentation, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Membership Coffees, 1984-1999
    Contained within the Membership Coffees subseries are event arrangements, hosts, and speakers for the coffees that the Women's Fund established to solicit, reward, and inform members about salient issues in women's health and medicine. Held at a member's home, these coffees offered information on women's health not generally discussed in public at the time that the Women's Fund was established. These events were an opportunity for women who volunteered in many organizations around Houston to afford themselves some time dedicated to women's concerns. Membership coffees were the site of announcements for annual grant awards that supported research and education projects. Documents related to the coffees are arranged chronologically.
    - Call for Hosts, 1984-1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Presentation of Research Grants, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Host: Joanne Wilson
    - George Blumenschein - Breast Cancer - Who is High Risk?, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Host: Janice McCrory
    - Jaimie Cochran - Coping with Orwell's 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Host: Marilyn Noll
    - Michael DeBakey - Heart Disease, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Host: Laura Lee Blanton
    - Jeff Sherman, Stella Garvan, and Peter Mansell - Straight Talk on AIDS, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Host: Sally Emde
    - Joanie Moncrief and Ann Hoy - Alcoholism, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Host: Rocky Franzen
    - Antonio Gotto - Heart Disease, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Host: Irene Weaver
    - Eugene Carlton - Common Bladder Problems in Women, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Host: Doris Buttram
    - Silver Tea - Debut of Women's Primer, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Host: Jeanette Jaworski
    - Sandra Sessoms - Systemic Lupus Erythematosus, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Host: Linda Finger
    - Raymond Kaufman - Questions to Ask Your Gynecologist, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Host: Emily Crosswell
    - Benjy Brooks - Successful Aging, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Host: Jacqueline Goettsche
    - Ann Richards - Alcoholism, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - John Wolf - Retin A, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Host: Andy Delery
    - J. P. McGehee - Even Cowgirls Get Holiday Blues, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Host: Jane Cizik
    - Ben Cooper - Headaches, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      Host: Jean Chernosky
    - Stephen Slade - Advances in Eye Care, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Host: Fay Burke